没有人告诉你活着有多累
∮ So no one told you life was gonna be this way ∮
上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘
∮ Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. ∮
寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累
∮ It's like you're always stuck in second gear ∮
日复一日 年复一年
∮ When it hasn't been your day, ∮
时运不济 活着受罪
∮ your week, your month, or even your year ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ but I'll be there for you ∮
纵有狂风暴雨
∮ When the rain starts to pour ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ I'll be there for you ∮
支持一如往昔
∮ Like I've been there before ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ I'll be there for you ∮
你我相偎相依
∮ 'Cause you're there for me too ∮
来自北京的班机 457号已经抵达
Flight number 457 from Beijing now arriving.
哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
哦 我的天啊
对不起 让开 让开… 有急事 拜托
Oh, my... Excuse me. Move, move, move! Emergency, please!
对不起
Excuse me, excuse me.
- 瑞秋   - 啊
- Rach!     - Ah!
总算找到你了
There you are!
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey!     - Hi!
噢 那 那…
Oh! So, so.
在中国还好吗？ 你哦
How was China? You!
- 很棒啊 怎么了？ - 什么？
- It was... It was great. Oh, what happened?     - What?
- 你在流血   - 有吗？
- You're bleeding.     - I am?
- 天啊   - 哦 你看看 真的有耶
- God.     - Oh, look at that! Yes, I am.
别管我了 这位从东方归来的先生
Enough about me, Mr. Back From The Orient!
快 有什么新鲜事统统告诉我 要一字不漏
come on, I wanna hear everything. Everying
嗯 我该从何开始呢？
Well, uh, where do I start? Um...
这位是茱莉 茱莉 这位是瑞秋
This is Julie. Uh, Julie, this is Rachel.
你好
Hi. Heh.
这束花是…
Uh, oh! These are...
- 这束花… 不是送你的   - 哦
- These are... Aren't for you.     - Oh.
是要送给你的
Heh. Uh, these are for you.
欢迎造访我国
Welcome to our country.
谢谢你 我是纽约人
Thank you. I'm from New York.
没关系 用来止血刚好
Well, not a problem. We'll use them to stop the bleeding.
好 要去领行李了吗？
Okay. Uh, baggage claim?
- 好   - 好
- Okay.     - Okay.
- 不可能   - 她去机场了
- No way.     - I'm telling you, she went to the airport.
她要去对罗斯下手了
And she's gonna go for it with Ross.
哇 我的天啊  这是大事 这…
Oh, my God. This is huge. This...
这比大事还大 这简直是…
This is bigger than huge. This is...
好吧 有什么比大事还大？
All right, what's bigger than huge?
- 就这件事？ - 对
- Um, this?     - Yes.
你们理新发型了
Guys, you got new haircuts!
对 我们理了 多亏了这位美发大师沙宣菲比
Yes, yes, we did. Thanks to Vidal Buffay.
因为"我们的光彩来自您的风釆"
Because, you know: "If you don't look good, we don't look good."
我爱死那个声音了
I love that voice!
- 你们大家   - 喔 瑞秋
- You guys!     - Oh, oh.
机场 机场 罗斯 有人陪
Airport. Airport. Ross. Not... Not alone.
茱莉 搂着她
Julie. Arm around her!
痛 痛 痛
Unh! Cramp! Cramp! Cramp!
我想她可能是想表达什么
Okay, I think she's trying to tell us something.
快 快找出句子的动词
Quick, get the verbs.
- 哦   - 你 你
- Ow.     - You! You!
你不是说他喜欢我吗？
You said he liked me! You! You...!
你们这两个慢半拍的
You slowpokes!
没错 行李全在我们手上
That's all right, Rach. We got the bags. Uh...
嗨  哈罗
Hi. Hello.
茱莉  她是我妹妹摩妮卡 他是钱德
Julie, this is my sister, Monica. This is Chandler.
- 嘿   - 菲比 嗨
- Hey.     - Phoebe, hi. Mwah.
- 乔伊 你还好吗？ - 哈罗
- Joey, what up?     - Hey.
- 大家注意 这位是茱莉   - 茉莉
- Everyone, this is Julie.     - Julie.
噢
Oh.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi!     - Hi!
就当我不在场 当我们根本没见过面
Hi! But I'm not here, you haven't met me.
如果没连坐20小时的飞机 我给人的第一印象会比较好
I'll make a better impression when I don't have 20 hours of plane on me.
- 还有搭巴士的时间   - 哦 我的天
- And bus.     - Oh, my God!
- 那个大叫的家伙…   - 吐口水的人
- With the screaming guy...     - And the spitting.
你们一定得听这件事
You gotta hear this story.
我们搭了一辆有200年之久的巴士
We're on this bus that's 200 years old.
最少200年
Two hundred, at least.
- 有个家伙…   - 后来鸡在她大腿上大便了
- And this guy...     - And the chicken poops in her lap! Ha!
真是对不起
Oh, I'm so sorry.
我把结局说出来了 是吗？
I just gave away the ending, didn't I?
我刚刚在计程车上 听过这个故事…
Ugh, I just heard this story in the cab...
然后我就再也忘不了
and it is all I can think about.
太令人意外了 怎么…
This is amazing. I mean, how...?
- 怎么会这样子的呢？ - 我们是在同一个研究所
- How did this happen?     - Ross and I were in grad school together.
毕业后就没见过面了 我一到中国
We haven't seen each other since then. I land in China...
你们猜负责的人是谁？
guess who's in charge of the dig?
茱莉
Julie!
这不是太妙了吗？
Julie. Isn't that great?
真是妙得让人想踹你一脚 再对着你的脖子吐口水
Isn't that just kick-you-in-the-crotch, spit-on-your-neck fantastic?
只是一种形容的方式
It's an expression.
我们只是很快的 来打声招呼
We just wanted to say a quick hi.
- 然后我们就要去看宝宝   - 然后睡一觉
- Then we're gonna go see the baby.     - Then get some sleep.
现在其实是明晚六点钟 我们的时差
Yeah, it's 6:00 tomorrow night, our time.
好 千万别告诉我明天会怎样 因为我喜欢惊喜
Well don't tell us what's gonna happen, though Because I like to be surprised.
- 再见    - 再见
- Bye!     - Bye.
(中央咖啡厅)
瑞秋 可以给我咖啡吗？
Rach. Can I get some coffee?
- 当然好   - 谢谢
- Sure.     - Thank you.
- 嘿 瑞秋…   - 你跟他说了没？
- Hey, Rach...     - Did you talk to him yet?
- 没   - 那就甭想喝
- No.     - Then, no.
你在中国到底发生什么事了？
So, what the hell happened to you in China?
上回我们离开这里的时候 你还爱着…
I mean, when last we left you, you were in love with, you know.
我知道 曾经是那样没错
I know. I know I was.
可是我心中一直有个声音 在提醒我…
But there was always this voice inside that kept saying:
"那是不可能的 你要往前走" 你知道那是谁的声音吧？
"It's never gonna happen. Move on." You know whose voice that was?
上帝吗？
God?
是你啊 老兄
It was you, pal.
也许是上帝在模仿我
Well, maybe it was God doing me.
你说得没错 在她眼里我只是一个朋友  就这样
You were right. She looks at me and sees a friend. That's all.
然后我就遇到茱莉 我们在一起很棒
And then I met Julie, and... I don't know. We're having a great time.
要不是你的话 我绝对不可能跟她在一起的
I never would have gone for it with her, if it hadn't been for you.
嗯 你欠我一个大人情了  大个儿
Well, you owe me one, big guy.
你的柠檬汁来了
Here's your lemonade.
我没叫啊
I didn't order lemonade.
那就拿回去还 不然他们会算钱的
Oh. Well then you better go take that back. They're gonna charge you for that.
- 但…   - 快 快 快 快点 快点
- But...     - Go, go, go! Come on, come on!
好 你有什么发现？
Okay, so, uh, what did you find out?
他说…
He said...
- 他说他们在一起很棒 抱歉   - 什么？
- He said they're having a great time. I'm sorry.     - What?
不过 只要你愿意用心看待 还是有一线希望的
But the silver lining, if you wanna see it...
也就是 这全是他自行决定的…
is that he made this decision all by himself...
绝对没有任何外来力量的协助
without any outside help whatsoever.
这样怎么会叫一线希望呢？
How is that a silver lining?
必须很用力 才能看到"一线"希望
You have to really wanna see it.
讽刺的是 这些家伙都是上体育课时没人愿意挑的
Ironically, these guys were picked last in gym.
嘿 菲比
Hey, Pheebs.
- 知道我在想什么吗？ - 哦 可以
- You know what I'm thinking?     - Oh, okay.
在想…
How...
你很久没跟人嘿咻了…
it's been so long since you've had sex...
所以你在想 现在有没有什么新花招？
you're wondering if they've changed it?
不是 不过现在 我真的在想这件事了
No. Although now that's what I'm thinking.
那你刚才在想什么？
So, what were you thinking?
你帮他们剪了很棒的发型 我在想你也可以帮我剪
I was thinking you gave the guys great haircuts. I thought you'd like to do mine.
哦 不要
Oh! No.
- 有何不可？ - 因为我只是…
- Why not?     - Because I'm just...
我是个控制狂 而且非常的挑剔
I'm incredibly anal and an unbelievable control freak.
- 不 你不是   - 我知道我不是 不过你是
- No, you're not.     - I know I'm not, but you are.
我只是不想伤你的感情
I was trying to spare your feelings.
喂 嗨 你好
Hello? Oh, hi.
好 罗斯 等一下 茱莉找你
Yeah, hold on a second. Ross, Julie for you.
喂 嗨
Hello? Hi.
嘿 有人认识什么好裁缝师吗？
Hey. Anybody know a good tailor?
- 有衣服要修改吗？ - 不是
- You need clothes altered?     - No, no.
我只是想找个人拿粉笔在我身上画
I'm just looking for a man to draw on me with chalk.
去找法兰克 我家的人总是找他
Go see Frankie. My family's been going to him forever.
我15岁时第一套西装就是他做的 不 等等 是16岁
He did my first suit when I was 15. No, wait, 16.
不 抱歉 是15岁
No, excuse me, heh, 15.
好吧 1990年到底是什么时候？
All right, when was 1990?
好吧 当棉花棒碰到东西 就别继续挖下去了
Okay, you have to stop the Q-Tip when there's resistance.
好 好的 甜心 我们持会儿见了
Okay. Okay. Sweetheart, I'll see you later.
好的 拜 什么？
Okay, bye. What?
喔 你真甜
Oh, that is so sweet.
不…
No... Ha, ha.
好 不 你先挂
No. Okay. No, you hang up.
不 你… 好吧
No, you... Okay. Okay.
一 二 三
One, two, three. Shh.
你也没啊
Well you didn't hang up either.
她没挂掉
She didn't hang up.
好吧 不行
Okay, no.
不 你来挂电话
No, you hang up.
你 你…
You. You. Yo...
抱歉 我还以为你是在对我说
Sorry, I thought you were talking to me.
- 瑞秋   - 对不起
- Rachel. Heh.     - Sorry.
- 我再打给她   - 好吧
- I'll just call her back.     - Okay.
对不起 刚刚断线了
Hi, sweetie. I'm sorry. We got disconnected.
不 你挂
No, you hang up.
好吧 我怎么会这样？
Okay, okay, okay. How did this happen to me? How?
一个礼拜前 两个礼拜前 我还好好的
A week ago, two weeks ago, I was fine.
罗斯只是罗斯 就是一个家伙
Ross was just Ross. Just this guy.
如今 突然间 他是罗斯…
Now all of a sudden, he's Ross...
是我无福拥有的好家伙
ugh, this really great guy that I can't have.
以前我也希望你能拥有他
Sweetie, I wanted you to have him too.
我知道
I know you did.
我会熬过去的
Ugh. I'm just gonna deal with it. I'm just gonna deal with it
我得离开这里
I gotta get out of here!
我不管你们怎么说 她真的有心事
I don't care what you guys say. Something's bothering her.
知道吗？我想我当年是16岁
You know, I think I was 16.
拜托 只要后面修一点点就好？
Please, just a little bit off the back.
我还是"不要"
Um, I'm still on "no."
- 早   - 嘿
- Uh, morning.     - Hey.
你们可以先闭上眼睛吗？
Could you close your eyes for a sec?
不 不 不 我不会再上你的当了
Oh, no, no, no. I'm not falling for that again.
- 怎么了？ - 我昨晚做了一件傻事
- What's going on?     - I sort of did a stupid thing last night.
什么傻事？
What stupid thing did you do?
巴洛 你去穿好衣服 然后就可以走了 再见
Why don't you just go get dressed...then you'll be on your way. Bye-bye.
瑞秋 怎么会这样？
Rachel, how did this happen?
我昨晚碰巧遇到他了
I don't know, I kind of ran into him last night.
- 在哪里遇到的？ - 他的公寓 这是果汁吗？
- Where?     - At his apartment. Is this juice?
喂 你忘了你甩他是因为他想钓菲比？
Whoa. And the fact that you dumped him because he hit on Phoebe?
哦 天啊 我晓得 我真可悲 我是个没用的人
Oh, God, I know. I'm pathetic, I'm a loser.
你不可悲 你只是悲伤
Honey, you're not pathetic. You're just sad.
伤心人总是会做傻事的
Yeah. People do stupid things when they're upset.
我的天 如果我因每个我不该上床的人而都得到五毛钱…
My God, if I had a nickel for every guy I wish I hadn't...
我们现在谈的是你犯下的大错
But this is about your horrible mistake.
- 嗨   - 嘿
- Hi.     - Hey!
- 嗨   - 抱歉我们迟到了
- Hi...     - Sorry we're late.
我们刚刚在…
We were, uh...
哦 是跟爱抚有关的
Well, there was touching.
- 嘿 罗斯   - 巴洛
- Hey, Ross!     - Paolo. Ha.
搞什… 嗯…？
What a...
你来这里干什么？
What, uh...? What are you doing here?
- 我来找瑞秋   - 恩
- I do Raquel.     - Ah.
这么说他回来了？
So, uh, he's back?
对 他回来了 有问题吗？
Yeah, he's back. Is that a problem?
不 没有问题
No, not a problem.
很好 很欣慰不构成问题
Good. Glad it's not a problem.
你必须别碰我的屁股
Okay, you're gonna have to not touch my ass.
嗯 尽管有美味的贝果 以及触手可及的紧张局势存在…
Well, despite the yummy bagels and palpable tension...
我还是得去改我的长裤
I've got pants that need to be altered.
看到法兰克的时候 跟他说乔伊崔比亚尼问候他
Oh, when you see Frankie, tell him Joey Tribbiani says hello.
这样子他就会懂了
He'll know what it means.
你确定他能解开如此深奥的谜题？
You sure he's gonna be able to crack that code?
真好玩 巴洛上次在这里时 我的头发还很短很可爱
It's funny. The last time Paolo was here, my hair was so much shorter and cuter.
好吧
All right. Okay.
但你得保证 你不会管太多 太唠叨…
But... But! You have to promise that you will not be all controlly and bossy...
还有别太摩妮卡就是了
and all, you know, Monica about it.
- 我保证   - 好 我看看
- I promise.     - All right, let's see.
好 你们有些会被修剪 有些不会
Now, some of you are gonna get cut and some of you aren't.
不过我保证 你们全都不会感到痛楚
But I promise, none of you will feel a thing.
好
Okay.
- 够了 我不干了   - 干嘛？我什么也没说
- All right, that's it. I quit.     - What? I didn't say anything!
但这不是相信人的表情
Yeah, but this isn't the face of a person who trusts a person.
这种表情是…
This is the face of a person who, you know...
不相信人的表情
doesn't trust a person.
我很抱歉 我很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Phoebe.
只是这比我们讨论的发型 短多了
It's just a little shorter than what we had discussed.
你放轻松好吗？ 我知道自己在做什么
Would you relax? I know what I am doing.
这就是那位先生的发型
This is how he wears it.
- 哪位的发型？ - 黛咪·摩尔
- How who wears it?     - Demi Moore.
黛咪·摩尔不是"先生"
Heh. Demi Moore is not a he.
哦 他在《二八佳人花公子》 和《十全十美》中是个"先生"
Well, he was a he in Arthur and in 10.
那个人是杜利·摩尔
That's Dudley Moore!
我说的是 我要黛咪·摩尔的发型
I said I wanted it like Demi Moore!
- 哦 哦   - 哦 我的天啊
- Oh. Oh!     - Oh, my God!
- 哦 天啊   - 哦 我的天啊
- Oh, God!     - Oh, my God!
哦 我的天 我很抱歉
Oh, my God! I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
黛咪·摩尔是哪一个啊？
Which one is Demi Moore?
她是《桃色机密》《桃色交易》 和《第六感生死恋》那个女星
She's the actress that was in Disclosure, Indecent Proposal, Ghost!
- 她的发型很棒的   - 我知道
- Oh, she's got gorgeous hair.     - I know!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
(量身订做裁缝)
- 裤管的褶边要多长？ - 要跟这条长裤的存活期一样长
- How long do you want the cuffs?     - At least as long as I have the pants.
我刚听懂
I just got that.
现在要量你的内侧长度
Okay. Now we'll do your inseam.
- 她的情况怎样？ - 现在还很难说
- How is she?     - It's too soon to tell.
她在休息了 起码这是一个好现象
She's resting, which is a good sign.
- 头发的情况呢？ - 我不想骗你
- How's the hair?     - I'm not gonna lie to you, Ross.
看起来不妙
It doesn't look good.
我有夹起一边 似乎能阻止卷曲情况
I put a clip on one side, which seems to have stopped the curling.
我们可以去看她了吗？
Can we see her?
你的发型看起来太棒了 反而会让她更难过
Your hair looks too good. It would upset her.
罗斯 何不由你进去看她？
Ross, why don't you come on in.
- 你还好吗？ - 我没事
- Well, how you doing?     - I'm okay.
- 那么糟吗？ - 什么？
- Ooh, that bad, huh?     - What?
我可以感受到女性挫折与无助的时刻
Look, I can sense when women are depressed and vulnerable.
这是我的天赋之一 坐
It's one of my gifts. Sit.
乔伊 当我看到他跟她下飞机的那一刻…
Ugh, Joey, when I saw him get off that plane with her...
我真的以为我已经沉到谷底了
I really thought I just hit rock bottom.
可是今天的感觉就像是有个谷底…
But today, it's like there's rock bottom...
然后下面还有50英尺的垃圾…
50 feet of crap...
然后才是我
then me.
把你的感觉告诉罗斯
You gotta tell Ross how you feel.
我怎么能去对他说？那茱莉怎么办？
Oh, come on, how can I just tell him? What about Julie?
她怎样？他们才在一起两星期
What about her? They've only been going out for two weeks.
罗斯已经爱你快十年了
Ross has been in love with you for 10 years.
- 我不知道 我不知道   - 瑞秋 瑞秋
- I don't know. I don't know.     - Look, Rach, Rach.
我有跟一些女性友人相处过
I've been with my share of women.
其实我有跟很多别人的女性友人相处过
I've been with a lot of people's share of women.
关键在于…
But the point is...
罗斯对你的感情是我不曾感受过的
I've never felt about anyone the way Ross felt about you.
真的？
Really?
喂 同志
Yo, paisan.
我可以跟你谈一下吗？
Can I talk to you for a sec?
你的裁缝师…
Your tailor...
是一个很坏的人
is a very bad man!
法兰克？你在说什么啊？
Frankie? What are you talking about?
嘿 怎么了？
Hey, what's going on?
乔伊的裁缝师…
Joey's tailor...
占我便宜
took advantage of me.
- 什么？ - 不可能
- What?     - No way.
我找他12年了
I've been going to the guy for 12 years.
他说他要量我的内侧长度
Oh, come on. He said he was gonna do my inseam.
然后他就沿着我的腿往上摸 然后就很明显的…
Then he ran his hand up my leg and then there was definite...
什么？
What?
捧来捧去的
Cupping.
他们量尺寸都是这样
That's how they do pants!
首先 会先从一边摸上去 然后会推到另一边去
First they go up one side, they move it over.
然后 再从另一边上来 再推回去 然后再量后面
Then they go up the other side, move it back, then they do the rear.
干嘛？罗斯 告诉他 裁缝师不都是这样量长裤的吗？
What? Ross, tell him. Isn't that how a tailor measures pants?
对 是这样没错 那是在牢里才这样量
Yes, yes, it is. In prison!
你有毛病啊？
What's the matter with you?
干嘛啦？
What?
不是那样子的吗？
That's not?
哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
即使是玛丽·泰勒·摩尔的发型 都比我好看
Even Mary Tyler Moore would've been better.
我喜欢这发型
I like it.
真的 我觉得这是"十全十美"
Yeah, I do. I think it's a 10!
谢谢你
Thank you.
我的头发很有趣味性
My hair is very amused.
得了 这也不是最惨的事
Oh, come on, things could be worse. I mean, uh...
你又没被"卡在月亮与纽约市之间"
You could "get caught between the moon and New York City.
我知道"很疯狂 不过那是真的"
I know it's crazy, but it's true."
真多谢
Thank you.
- 嗯 我得走了 再见   - 待会儿见
- Well, I gotta go. Bye.     - See you.
- 再见 瑞秋   - 等等 你要走了？
- Bye, Rach!     - Wait, are you leaving?
我说"再见"就是这个意思
That's what I meant by "bye."
- 我可以跟你谈一下下吗？ - 好
- Well, uh, can I talk to you for a sec?     - Okay.
医生做疝气检查的时候…
When the doctor does that hernia test...
那是可以的
That's okay.
- 有什么事吗？ - 嗯…
- What's going on?     - Um...
- 嗯 好 首先…   - 嗯
- Well, um, okay, first of all...     - Mm-hm.
巴洛和我并没有复合
Paolo and I are not back together.
那只是我干的一件傻事
That was a stupid thing I did.
如果我能回到过去 再有机会选择的话…
If I could go back in time and do it again...
嗯 我就不会做傻事
well, I wouldn't.
其次呢
Second of all...
干嘛？
What?
好吧
OK.
我发言前先问你一下
Before I say anything I just need to know...
是否就像是 你跟一个人分手…
is this one of those things where you break up with a guy.
然后我对你说出我的看法 然后你隔日就又跟他复合
Then I tell you what I think... ...and the next day you get back together with him...
- 然后我就变成一个大傻瓜？ - 不是
- and I look like a complete idiot?     - No, no, no.
好吧
Okay.
好 那么 我觉得那家伙是个大浑球
Um, well, then, I think the guy's scum.
我讨厌他 我真的… 真的很恨他
I hate him. I mean, I actually... I physically hate him.
我一直是这种感觉
You know? I always have.
你太棒了 他配不上你
And you are way too good to be with a guy like that.
- 真的？ - 瑞秋？
- Really?     - Rach?
你值得一个能欣赏你的男人…
You deserve to be with someone who appreciates you...
一个能了解你的 风趣 甜美 神奇…
and who gets how funny... ...and sweet and amazing...
了解你的可爱与性感的男人
and adorable and sexy you are.
你知道吗？ 就是一个会在每天醒来就想着…
You know? Someone who wakes up every morning thinking:
"哦 我的天 我跟瑞秋在一起 "
"Oh, my God. I'm with Rachel!" Heh.
知道吗？ 就是一个能让你感觉很棒的人
You know? Someone who makes you feel good.
就像我对茱莉的感觉一样
Like the way I do with Julie.
还有什么"其次"的话吗？
Was there a "second of all"?
不 我想就这些了
No, um, I think that was the whole "all."
我得走了 好吗？
I gotta go. Okay?
- 好   - 谢谢
- Okay.     - Thanks.
好
Okay.
不 我对天发誓 老爸 别人不是那样子量裤长的
No, I swear to God, Dad! That's not how they measure pants!
我想剪个较短的发型 就像安蒂·麦道威尔那样
I was thinking of doing it shorter, like Andie MacDowell's haircut.
- 可以 我会剪   - 真的？
- Oh, yeah. Oh, I could do that.     - Really?
- 没问题 你要现在就剪吗？ - 太棒了
- Yeah. You wanna do it now?     - Great!
- 好啊   - 好啊
- Okay.     - Okay.
再见
See you.
好吧 这次我想要确定一下
Okay, I just wanna make really sure this time. Uh-huh. Ahem.
安蒂·麦道威尔是《你是我今生的新娘》里那个女的 对吧？
Andie MacDowell is the girl from Four Weddings and a Funeral, right?
不是
No.
不是 那是洛帝·麦道威尔
No, no, no, no, no, no. That's Roddy McDowall.
安蒂·麦道威尔是在《决战猩球》里演人猿的那个家伙
Andie MacDowell is the guy from Planet of the Apes.
- 哦 对   - 对 好吗？
- Oh! Yeah, okay.     - Yeah. Okay?
- 谢谢   - 不客气
- Thank you.     - You're welcome.